Hi people. By now, you probably have
seen the video that uh Iran put out
today
where
they show individuals looking up.
And each image of each individual
represents a country that the US has had
a war with.
They portray those individuals as
victims.
And they are all looking up.
Towards the end of the video,
uh
they show a missile,
a Iranian missile. The missile actually
has the flag of Iran stamped uh on it.
And it reaches New York.
And hits what symbolizes
the Statue of Liberty.
But,
if you pay very close attention,
the Statue of Liberty doesn't have the
face that it has.
It has the face of a bull.
Of a bull.
And basically,
the missile
>> [snorts]
>> hits
the the
Statue of Liberty
at its feet.
And it crumbles down.
So, I have seen actually few uh few
people here on on Tik Tok showing the
video, saying a bunch of stuff, but
nobody has said this.
And this is the very first thing that
came to my mind.
Daniel 2.
There was a statue there. In Daniel 2,
there's a prophecy there.
That
part of the prophecy
has not been fulfilled.
>> [snorts]
>> And the statue
is like this.
The head is made of gold, Babylonia.
The chest and arms of silver, the
Medo-Persia empire.
In Persia is Iran, is Elam in in
Jeremiah 49 today,
Iran.
Then the belly and thighs is made of a
uh
bronze.
And that's Greece.
And the legs
are made of iron, and that's Rome.
But, the feet is very interesting
because the feet is made of iron
and clay. And this kind of clay is a is
a specifically that doesn't matter what
you do, it doesn't come together. It
doesn't
mix and become a strong clay.
Um
meaning that this empire, this last
empire, is divided.
Then what happens is that a rock, not
cut by human hands,
comes from
uh
heaven.
And hits the statue where?
At the feet. Exactly where
the iron and the clay and the clay
itself does not mix.
The rock represents the kingdom of God.
The Iranians
most likely read the book of Daniel.
And what they are trying to say there is
this, and maybe you need to understand.
This is a spiritual war. This is a
spirit It's not a religious war. They
may They may try to make this a
religious war where Christians and and
and Jews
come together against against Islam. No,
it's not that.
It is a war,
a spiritual war, where
evil is trying to make a point,
probably using the Bible itself, just
like Satan can use the Bible against try
to use the Bible against Jesus. And
Jesus was tempted.
The Iranians, as I said, they most
likely read the Bible.
And what they are saying to a certain
extent very true,
that
the feet of the Statue of Liberty,
representing the US,
is an empire that is divided. And do you
know what? The US is divided.
Now, I don't think they're right because
they are not from God.
Um
They're certainly not from God.
They, meaning the Iranians.
But, what they are
What they are attempting to do here
is to tell the world, and the world that
knows anything about prophecy,
Christian or Muslim,
that they have
the hand of God
with them
to destroy
the statue
and begin a new
world order.
If you have read in the book of Daniel,
you know that there is a time that
Daniel prayed for something.
And there is no answer. There's no
answer. There's no answer.
21 days later, Gabriel comes and says,
"Hey, I got here finally. Because on my
way down,
the prince of Persia
kind of uh
fought with me. He would not allow me to
come down.
And then Michael came to my rescue, and
Michael fought him, and he defeated the
prince of Persia.
And Daniel, here I am.
Do not think
that the prince of Persia
that is um
that Daniel talks about in his book.
Don't think that the prince of Persia
has disappeared.
He continues to be
the prince of Persia.
He's one of the watchers.
He's still working on the behalf
of Persia.
Of Iran.
And do you know what the problem is?
Israel
denies Jesus Christ.
And the US have a good talk.
But,
if you pay very close attention, all
these leaders,
they
their praise,
their recognition of God, is only from
their mouth, not from their heart.
So, here we go.
You have a lost nation of Israel.
You have a lost nation of America
going against the prince
that is still powerful,
the prince of
Persia.
Do you know who can stop him?
Michael.
Jesus Christ.
Do you know
how
the possibility for Jesus Christ to stop
this watcher
is if at least one of us
pray like Daniel prayed.
One of us.
This may very well be
the beginning of the end.
This is prophetic.
This is serious.
And let me say this.
Don't think that by praying you're going
to stop prophecy.
Otherwise, Jesus will never come back.
This world This world will never end.
And then
that would make the Bible a lie.
Jesus can stop the prince of Persia
for the sake of his people.
The
the ones that are chosen from the nation
of Israel, because not all Israel is
chosen.
Let me rephrase this.
It is, but most of them have rejected
the Messiah.
But then, there is another people,
we, the church.
And Jesus would just stop the prince of
Persia to save the chosen within the
chosen people of Israel, and to save the
chosen the
the true Christian.
Still,
prophecy must be fulfilled.
The Iran Iranians
read the Bible.
And most people
are missing what this video is actually
saying.
Most people are actually missing the
message,
which is
the prince of Persia
that one day defeated
was defeated by Michael
has come back
to defeat the most powerful nation in
the world.